Hey. Victim's name is John Flynn.
He's 48, married... Cho's
bringing the wife now...
And C.E.O. of a company
called Symphony.
Symphony?
Web site says it's a high-end
matchmaking service.
Rich old men looking for hot young chicks?
Yep. Flynn was shot twice
in the chest at close range
then dumped or fell in the water.
A woman heard some pops
from her boat
putting the time of death
at 5:38 P.M. last night.
- Did she see anything?
- No. No witnesses.
- Bruising looks to be a few days old.
- Coroner thought the same.
So far he and forensics haven't
found much else that helps us.
Jane, anything to add before we go?
Yeah, the sun and the sea...
isn't it wonderful?
Anything to add about the victim?
Rich guy, C.E.O.
probably killed over money.
- Way of the world.
- That's all you got?
Do you know in seven years, each and every
cell is completely replaced in your body?
That means you are literally a different
person from when we first met.
Sadder but wiser.
He's very wet.
That must mean something.
- Grieving widow?
- Yeah.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- You were watching me.
- Yes.
- Why?
- It's my job.
Your husband was murdered
at the marina last night.
Yes.
- Sorry for your loss.
- Thank you.
- You seem genuinely upset.
- Does that surprise you?
How long were you
and your husband married?
- I'm sorry. I don't know your name.
- Patrick.
Erica. About a year.
What do you see?
You're independent,
ambitious, competitive
yet you have a warmth about you...
Enough to charm the stoic agent Cho
which is no small feat, let me tell you.
You're skilled at getting people
to open up to you, to trust you.
And there's a question of whether
you use that skill to help people
or to manipulate them.
A little of both, if I'm being honest.
I'm a matchmaker.
I help people find true love.
- You think it's silly.
- No. Good enough job, I imagine.
- You think the idea of true love is silly.
- No.
- That explains it.
- Explains what?
The utter sadness I see in you.
We're all finished, Mrs. Flynn.
I could walk you out, if you like.
Thank you, agent Cho.
You've been very good to me.
- I'll walk her out, if you don't mind.
- Not at all.
Sure.
It was very nice to meet you, Patrick.
Hopefully next time,
it'll be under better circumstances.
You know, every day women come to me
hoping I'll help them find a kind,
gentle man to fall in love with.
I'm sure any one of them
would be lucky to meet you.
What was that all about?
Oh, she's just thanking me
for consoling her.
Oh, and here I thought you
hated talking to widows.
- This one's a little different.
- How so?
She murdered her husband.
You're right. Usually, it's the victim's
spouse who's the murderer
but Erica Flynn has an alibi.
I'd expect nothing less from her.
One of her clients is in
with Rigsby right now
and she swears that she was with
Erica at the time of death.
Then I must be wrong.
She did say that her husband
got in a fight a few days ago
he came home with a bruise.
- She doesn't know who the fight was with.
- Any guesses?
The reality is John Flynn ran
a multi-million dollar company.
He had money, dozens of employees
and a lot of ruthless competitors.
And Flynn's file also says that he gave
half a million dollars to charity last year.
That's the first time
he's ever done that.
- So?
- It's a red flag.
- How is giving to charity a red flag?
- Giving to charity isn't a red flag.
Giving half a million dollars
to charity, out of the blue, is.
It's a sure sign of a guilty conscience.
That is so far from the truth.
Well, think about the people that donate
that kind of money to charity...
All right, Wall Street executives,
crooked politicians, troubled celebrities...
It is all in the name of
clearing their conscience.
You're horrible.
How long have you been
a member of Symphony?
Oh, just a few days, actually.
Night before last was my first
interview with Erica.
- And what time was this?
- From 05:00 until just after 6:00.
And you're convinced that Erica Flynn
was there the entire time?
- Yes.
- Can anyone confirm that?
Oh, I think the rest of the staff
had already left the office
by the time we started.
I'm a litigator, so that was the
earliest I could meet Erica.
Oh, it's probably why I joined
the service in the first place.
It's not that I'm some
social leper or anything.
I mean, I can meet people.
I meet people all the time.
So... no?
No.
But there's the DVD.
- The DVD?
- Of the interview.
Yeah, it's part of,
uh, Symphony's service.
A client interview, appearance
counseling, date coaching.
It's actually a very thorough
approach to matchmaking.
Anyway, Erica was interviewing
me the whole time.
Just see for yourself.
Just... just... God, don't show it
to too many people
'cause it's kind of embarrassing.
And they haven't edited out
all my silly faces, dumb comments yet.
Oh, my God. Okay, it's fine.
You can watch it.
I mean, for investigative
purposes, obviously
not that if you wanted to watch it
for other reasons you couldn't.
Got it. Uh, well, we'll call
with any other questions.
- Thanks for your time.
- Okay, right. Well, no, thank you.
All right, I-I had...
I have a question.
I... will just...
Are you in a relationship?
No. I'm... I'm not, actually.
Well... good to know.
- Uh, nice to meet you, agent Rigsby.
- Nice to meet you, Sarah.
- This way.
- Right.
Hey, boss.
You gotta see this.
It's a video of John Flynn's
ex-wife, Kim Cartwright.
I found it online while doing background.
"3 months ago, my husband of 21 years
John Flynn, told me he was divorcing me."
"John said he wanted to be alone that
he didn't want to be married anymore."
"Well, John, this is what I think
of your settlement agreement."
"Word is out on you, John.
I am going to tell everyone"
"exactly what kind of a man you are"
"because you are a pig!
You are a coward!"
"I made that video over a year ago.
I was upset."
You were more than upset, Ms. Cartwright.
You threatened to make your
ex-husband's life miserable.
Talk to me when your
ex-husband remarries
someone ten years younger
and two sizes smaller.
Libby, no, no. No barking.
- Where were you that night?
- I was home alone.
I didn't kill John,
if that's what you're thinking.
Oh, my God. That's what you're thinking.
That's insane!
John and I reconciled months ago.
We... we spoke all the time.
Including the afternoon he was murdered.
Do you recall what you two talked about?
John was unhappy in his marriage
and he needed someone to listen.
- So he called his ex-wife?
- Okay, it's complicated, all right?
Shh. Shh. Bad dog. Shh. No bark.
You said John was unhappy in his marriage.
Why?
Well, John loved his company
but he was ready
to step back and enjoy life
and Erica didn't feel that way.
She kept pushing him
to expand Symphony.
- It caused problems between them.
- Shh!
When we found John,
he had a bruise over his left eye.
He mentioned that he'd gotten into a fight
with an ex-client, Henry Cliff.
- You know what the fight was about?
- No, he was evasive.
It was something
he didn't wanna share.
Did you know Erica Flynn signed a prenup
before she got married?
You're barking up the wrong tree.
Time stamp puts the start
of the meeting at 5:00 P.M.
It finishes just after 6:00,
just like Sarah said
which means that Erica
Flynn was at her office
- at the time of the murder.
- "Try to look directly into camera."
"It will allow your future soul mate
to better connect with you."
What do you think of these dating
services anyway?
- No and yes.
- What?
No, I've never used
one, and yes, you should.
Oh, because you're cool, and I'm not?
Anything to stop you
dating your co-workers.
"How would your closest
friends describe you"
- "to someone who doesn't know you?"
- "Oh. Well, I think they would say..."
"Uh, we have you scheduled
to come in next Tuesday."
Okay, great. See you then.
Welcome to Symphony.
If you'll just fill out this profile
someone will be with you shortly.
Profile.
Patrick. I see you two have met.
Peter's our reception clerk,
though I doubt for much longer.
He's a very talented musician,
writes such beautiful music.
Patrick is a consultant with CBI.
He's investigating John's murder.
I'll hold your calls.
We're all a little overwhelmed
today, as you can imagine.
I shouldn't even be here.
But to be honest, I didn't
have much of a choice.
With John gone, well, you understand.
- Is there any news in the investigation?
- No.
- Do you have any more questions for me?
- Not really.
- I think I understand.
- Understand what?
Why you're here. I wasn't sure at first
when I saw your ring
- but you're single, aren't you?
- That's not why I'm here.
There's nothing to be ashamed of, Patrick.
I've helped a great many clients
in the exact same situation as you.
Well, I'm not in a situation.
There's no situation.
I know what you're feeling.
I've been there.
Yeah, I don't think you have.
You were in a relationship
once, you were in love
but it ended badly, and you
were deeply hurt as a result.
You shut yourself off from the world
and avoid meeting new people
because you don't want
to ever feel that loss again.
But now you're ready to move on
with your life.
I can see it in you.
You can find happiness
again, even true love
but you have to be willing
to let me help you.
That was spooky.
It was like you read my mind.
Our in-house studio is right this way.
It's where we conduct
our client interviews.
How many interviews
have you conducted here?
Enough to know what I'm doing.
Whoa. That's bright.
Very fancy.
We like to show our clients
in the best possible light.
I thought true love was blind.
We may love with our hearts,
but first we lust with our eyes.
Don't you agree?
If you make yourself comfortable,
we can get started.
- Here? Okay.
- Yeah.
Try to look directly into the camera.
It will allow your future soul mate
to better connect with you.
- "How's that?"
- "Perfect."
"I'm gonna ask you a series
of standardized questions."
"These have been designed
to get at the heart of who you are"
and who you're compatible with.
Try to answer as honestly as possible.
- Ready? Good.
- Yes.
Now, Patrick what kind of woman
are you interested in?
"Rich, quiet blondes."
"No snoring. That's a deal-breaker."
We were told you
punched out John Flynn.
Yeah, I hit John.
- It was a misunderstanding.
- Who misunderstood what?
- It was nothing, a tiff.
- Two days before he was murdered.
Am I under arrest?
No, you're just a person of interest
at this point a suspect.
Unless you can clear things up
with a simple explanation.
All right.
It was about a woman, okay?
Naomi.
Met her at a singles mixer
John's company organized.
We hit it off at the bar,
a few drinks, few laughs.
Next thing I know,
she invites me up to her room.
All right?
I'm up there, what, two seconds
boom... she is all over me.
I mean, really hot and really passionate.
Get to the part where you
punch out John Flynn.
Yeah, right.
Uh, two days later, I get a phone call.
I think she wants another bite
off the old Cliff bar, right?
No. Turns out the bitch
is blackmailing me.
Says she videotaped
our whole night together.
Says unless I give her $15,000
she's going public with that video.
You paid the money?
Well, yeah.
I can't have a sex tape going around.
Look, I'm a Sac Metro
top ten prestige realtor.
My face is on the friggin' billboard.
I get respect in this community.
So you went after Flynn.
He's supposed to be screening
these women, for Pete's sake.
But look, it's not what you think.
John and I talked it out.
He swore to me that he would
handle it personally
said he was gonna make sure
she got caught
and put in jail for what she did.
So much for that plan, right?
"I have just one more question."
"In an ideal world, what would
you want your life to be like?"
"Haven't thought about that."
"In an ideal world?"
"A pet dragon, definitely"
"for flying around on.
That would be good."
"Please try and answer seriously.
It's important."
What do you want from your life?
I want my life to be free.
Free how? To love? To be loved?
Free from my past.
I wanna tell you something.
Every day I introduce men
and women to one another.
If I do my job well,
those people connect.
They spark.
I can actually see it.
Just like I see it in
you right now with me.
I don't say this to make
you uncomfortable.
I say it because I want you to know
no matter how alone you feel
you are capable of finding
love, of moving on.
I was wondering when you'd do this.
- Do what?
- Try to manipulate me.
I would never do that.
I'm simply pointing out emotions
I know you feel towards me.
You're wrong. I don't feel anything
like that towards you
for one very good reason...
You murdered your husband.
- That's not funny.
- It wasn't meant to be.
Why would I kill my husband?
Money, well, money and control
of the company.
Same difference, really.
John was gonna leave you and if he left,
the company left with him.
Everything that you worked for,
everything that you'd built...
Gone.
And you couldn't let that happen.
No.
You're all about autonomy, control.
Abused as a child, I expect.
I didn't kill my husband.
In fact, you don't actually
believe I did.
- No?
- No.
You're simply doing what you've been
doing ever since your wife died...
Intentionally sabotaging
any relationship
by pushing away anyone who
makes you feel something.
You want me to be the killer
because you don't want
to have feelings for me.
It's a tragic but natural response
to the guilt you feel
over your wife's death.
I do push people away
and I do feel guilt over my wife's death
but that does not change the fact
that you murdered your husband.
I am more certain of it now than ever.
If that's the case
prove it.
Where are we with the Flynn murder?
Rigsby and I are still checking out
Henry Cliff's alibi.
He said he was in a bar
watching the game
but we still haven't found
anyone to confirm it.
Stay on it. What about the ex-wife?
Still no alibi either,
but I did find a lawsuit
Kim Cartwright filed against Flynn
around the same time
she posted that online video.
Looks like it has something to do
with the divorce settlement.
I'm having the courthouse
messenger over the files.
And the blackmailer, Naomi?
Yeah, we're having some
trouble tracking her down.
Symphony doesn't
have that information?
It's all fake... photos, driver's license,
social security number.
I mean, the forgery's good,
so I can see how they missed 'em.
All we have is Cliff's description of her
including a small tattoo near her hip.
So basically, we have nothing to go on.
Okay, let's start with what
we do know about Naomi.
Uh, she targeted a rich, single man
- with the purpose of extorting him, right?
- Right.
So if she's done it once,
she's probably done it before.
Van Pelt, check into every
dating service in the bay area.
"See if they've had any experience
with Naomi."
- "Maybe we can get to her that way."
- "On it."
There are 11 matchmaking services
in the bay area
four of which specifically
cater to high-end clients.
- Did they know Naomi?
- No.
And none have reported
any extortion claims
but I got to thinking
what if she's planning
to blackmail again?
I checked with the companies
in the area
and one is planning
a singles mixer tonight.
On a hunch, I cross-checked
Naomi's profile
from Symphony
with all the profiles of the women
listed as attending the event.
I got a match... a woman
named Viktoria Shays.
No photo, but several answers
she gave about herself
are identical to Naomi's.
- Is Rigsby here?
- Yeah, somewhere.
Tell him to go home
and put on a nice suit.
- He's got plans tonight.
- All right.
- Have you seen my laptop?
- No.
"Now, Sarah, what kind of men
are you interested in?"
"Wow, right to it."
"Now, Patrick what kind of woman
are you looking for?"
"Quiet, rich blondes.
No snoring. That is a deal-breaker."
"How would your closest friends describe you
to someone who doesn't know you?"
"Oh. Uh, well, I think they..."
"Now, Patrick, what kind of
woman are you looking for?"
"Quiet, rich blondes.
No snoring. That is a deal-breaker."
"Now, Sarah, what kind of men
are you interested in?"
"Wow, right to it."
So what do you think?
- I think you look good.
- Thank you. Cho?
I'm not answering that question.
Oh come on.
Honestly, just tell me what you think.
- You look all right.
- Thanks.
I think you look great
like you have money, a career...
- A perfect target for Naomi.
- I don't know.
What if she doesn't go for it?
- She will.
- What if she doesn't go for me?
I mean, there's gonna be
a lot of single guys there.
For this to work,
she has to be interested in me.
- She will. Just be yourself.
- That's a terrible idea.
Maybe I should do an accent
or something.
I don't think you need an accent.
Hello. Rigsby.
Wayne Rigsby from Sussex.
Uh, pleasure to meet you.
Cheerio.
- How's that?
- Yeah, don't do the accent.
Rigsby, can you hear me?
Loud and clear.
- "Van Pelt, you in position?"
- I'm here.
Gentlemen.
Can I have your attention?
It's time for me to bring in the beautiful
women you'll be meeting tonight.
Don't forget the a-b-c's...
Attentiveness, boldness, confidence.
You'll do great.
Rigsby, the event hostess
has I.D.'d Naomi.
Excuse me one moment.
Okay, which one is she?
The blonde in the lavender sheath.
- The one in the what now?
- The blonde in the purple dress.
Got it.
"Are you sure it's her?"
No. Find out if she's got
a rose tattoo on her hip.
- Then we'll know for sure.
- I'm moving in.
Hello, red.
- Can I buy you a drink?
- I'm engaged.
- Well, it's never too late for one last...
- Keep walking.
Okay.
Hi. I'm Wayne.
I'm Viktoria.
Nice to meet you.
So what do you do, Wayne?
I'm a businessman.
E-commerce, mainly.
How's that going for you?
It's working out pretty well.
I have a very diverse portfolio.
And I have a room upstairs.
- And you're very direct.
- Is that a problem?
I'm trying to think of a reason
why it might be
- and I can't really think of one right now.
- It's good.
- Are you nervous?
- Me? No.
Yeah, maybe a little.
Well, don't be. I won't bite.
Good. Me either. No biting.
3-1-6... my favorite number.
3-1-6.
Uh, just curious, uh, do
you have any tattoos?
Um, why don't you come and find out?
Okay.
So come in.
Make yourself comfortable.
I'll be right out.
Thanks.
Guys? You hear me?
She's in the bathroom.
Wow. That is a, um
very... nice tattoo.
Of a rose.
It's a rose tattoo.
Maybe we should have a drink first
or, uh, you know, uh...
A snack.
So would you call yourself
adventurous, Wayne?
Adventurous?
Um, what, like skydiving?
No.
Uh, sorry to interrupt.
CBI.
Uh, yeah, found the, uh, tattoo.
This is definitely the suspect.
Nice work.
Yeah. Your collar.
Your arrest, Wayne.
Oh, yeah.
You're under arrest.
Patrick.
I'm surprised to see you're back.
Are you here to finish your profile?
No.
I saw something strange
on the DVD you're using as your alibi
so I came by to test out a theory.
So you're still trying to prove
I murdered my husband?
You're still worried I will?
Come on in.
Why don't you have a seat?
You wanna interview me?
Why?
Like I said, I have a theory. You scared?
No.
It might be good
for me to experience
what my clients go through.
You can ask questions
from in there, yes?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- "What have you got up your sleeve?"
- Patience.
Okay.
- Can you hear me?
- Yes.
Okay, Erica
tell me, what kind of man
are you looking for?
I'm not looking. I'm mourning.
Yes. Uh, please humor me.
Someone kind
and generous
someone patient.
I'm sorry. I'm really not comfortable
talking about this.
Patrick?
"How would your closest friends
describe you"
- "to someone who doesn't know you?"
- Patrick, what are you doing?
"How would you describe yourself"
to someone who doesn't know you?"
What's going on in here?
I'm proving my theory.
I heard a strange sound on the DVD
you're using as your alibi...
A faint clicking noise.
Almost mechanical.
Then I figured out what it was.
"How would you describe
yourself to some..."
A simple tape recorder
just like this one.
I knew you weren't
here for the interview.
How could you be?
You're off killing your husband.
But how do we explain
your voice on the DVD?
- This is ridiculous.
- Recording the interview is easy.
After all, you've done hundreds of them.
And once you had the recorder in place
you had plenty of time to leave through
that door, kill your husband
and come back here without
anyone noticing you're gone.
But there is one thing you needed
in order for your plan to work...
an accomplice.
You needed someone to be here
and to play the recorded questions
at the right time.
That's the one loose end you left untied.
That explains it, doesn't it?
Of course there's just one problem.
So if what you're saying is true
I walked out right past my client
in the middle of her interview.
Something she would
have mentioned, huh?
I didn't kill my husband, Patrick.
I do understand.
After all you've been through,
you see evil everywhere.
- I see you.
- Patrick.
You are a kind, clever, wonderful man.
You have so much potential.
But you have to stop
this obsessive behavior.
You need to get a life.
Good night, Erica.
Good night, Patrick.
All you've proven is that Erica Flynn
may have murdered her
husband, not that she did.
Which is why I need to find
her accomplice.
- If there is an accomplice.
- There's no "if".
Yes, there is. We've got other
viable suspects on this thing.
- Like who?
- Like Naomi, for one.
Naomi? She's a greedy opportunist
that hates men.
- She's not a cold-blooded killer.
- We don't know that for sure.
You always say that the simplest answers
usually are the most likely
but it seems like you're coming up
with more and more elaborate scenarios
just to prove that you're right.
Erica killed her husband.
I am 100% sure of it.
I don't get it.
What is it about this woman?
Why are you so obsessed with her?
Because she doesn't think
I'm smart enough to catch her.
- Oh, well, that's a good reason.
- Yeah.
Healthy. Professional.
Uh, just answer me one more thing.
Okay, if Erica Flynn did
murder her husband
how did she leave the room
without her client noticing?
That I don't know.
But I'm working on it.
You're going to jail, Naomi.
Nothing can prevent that
from happening
but you can help yourself out here.
Tell me what you know about John Flynn.
Nothing.
I've never even met him.
Now we both know that's not true.
John Flynn ran Symphony.
He found out you were blackmailing his
clients and confronted you, didn't he?
I never blackmailed anyone.
But we have multiple victims
who claim otherwise.
We have the video camera
you hid in your hotel room
with other victims on it.
You watched that tape?
Did any of those guys
look like victims to you?
They look like John's being
conned by a clever prostitute.
I'm not a prostitute.
Where were you between
the hours of 5:00 and 6:00
- the night of the murder?
- I want my lawyer.
- I've got nothing more to say to you.
- Okay.
But we're waiting on a warrant
to search your apartment.
You talk now, we can make a deal.
We find anything linking you to the murder
all bets are off.
Lawyer.
Uh, yes, Erica interviewed
me from the A.V. room
- but she never left.
- Are you sure?
Yes. She would've had
to walk right past me.
What are you doing?
During your interview do you remember
how bright the lights were in that room?
- Yes.
- Shining right in your face, in fact.
Well, I guess so.
Yes, I once had a job onstage.
I'll never forget how
bright those lights can be.
What does that have to do
with anything?
I'll show you.
Keep your eye on your phone.
What are you doing?
It's gone.
Precisely.
- Hey, is that Sarah still here?
- Why?
Just had a few, follow-up questions
about the investigation.
You're such a bad liar.
She left five minutes ago.
Really?
Just call her up and ask her out.
What's the big deal?
I can't do that.
It's totally unprofessional.
Unless she says yes.
I think she'd say yes.
I mean, she asked me if I was single.
Why would she ask if I was single
unless she wanted me
to ask her out, right?
Sarah, hi. It's, uh,
Wayne Rigsby from CBI.
If you keep up with these visits
I'm gonna have to start charging you.
Oh, this will be the
last one, I assure you.
Have you given up on this nonsense
about me killing my husband?
Nope, not at all. Not one little tiny bit.
Well, then you must have
cracked the case.
Please tell me. I'm curious to know
who this evil accomplice of mine is.
Well, I came by it rather
easily, I must say
after a-a friend got me
thinking on the right path.
Which path is that?
The simplest answer is most
likely the correct one
which means your accomplice is
someone you can easily manipulate...
A man, which is obvious enough
given your physical attributes.
- I'm really getting tired...
- I'm not finished.
He's also young and
impressionable, weak
but above all, someone you can
make fall in love with you
and someone naive enough to believe
that you had fallen in love with them.
Guess who I'm thinking of.
Yes, that's right.
Your assistant Peter.
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
Ah, we'll find out soon enough.
What's going on?
Mrs. Flynn, we'd like you to
come back to the office with us
answer a few questions.
Of course. Anything to help.
How long do you think it'll take
before he tells me everything?
- How you holding up, Peter?
- I'm tired.
Ah, not to worry.
You won't be here much longer.
I know you're not gonna talk,
and I know why.
You're in love with Erica.
No, that's okay.
You don't need to deny it.
I get it.
She's beautiful, she's smart
she's successful.
- Makes you wonder, though, right?
- Wonder what?
What she sees in you.
Apart from her alibi.
I mean, let's be honest here, Peter.
You don't really have that much
to offer her.
- That's not true.
- Oh, so you are having an affair.
- I-I-I did not say that.
- Right.
We're being honest here, Peter.
Deep down, do you really think
that she loves you?
Or are you just kidding yourself
because it feel so nice to be with her?
- No. I love her, and she loves me.
- She was using you.
- She made you an accessory to murder.
- You're wrong.
She got what she wanted from you
- and now she is done with you.
- Stop. Stop saying that.
She doesn't love you, Peter.
She never did.
Now tell me what happened the night
Erica murdered her husband.
She problem told you that
he was abusing her, right?
- Smacking her around, raping her?
- I don't care what you say.
I'm not gonna hurt Erica.
What do we do now?
Jane?
Let him go.
- Hi, Wayne.
- Oh, hey. Wow. You look amazing.
Oh, thanks. So do you.
- Oh, are you ready to go?
- Yeah.
I was hoping you'd call me.
- Yeah, I'm glad I did.
- Me, too.
Hard at work, I see.
What do you want?
I'd like to thank you for having me
brought down here.
That was very courteous of you.
Though I have to admit,
I was a little surprised
your colleagues decided
to simply let me go
you being so certain
of my guilt and all.
Let me guess...
Peter didn't say a word to you?
Maybe now you'll be able
to move past this nonsense.
Let me tell you something...
I will catch you
sooner or later
and I promise you that I will catch you.
Please. If you were capable of catching me
you would have done so by now.
Good-bye, Patrick.
Jane. Jane, we gotta go.
I just got a call from
S.F.P.D. Peter's dead.
He killed himself.
Sleeping pills.
Coroner found an empty
bottle in the bathroom.
So... sole accomplice in your crime
just went and killed himself.
Fortunately, however
Peter left a letter.
And I'm betting it will tell us
everything we need to know
about the night your husband
was murdered.
You confess now chances are the A.G.'s
office is gonna cut you a deal.
Open it. I don't believe you.
Be my guest.
Yes, it's a bluff.
Honestly, I expected better from you.
Using poor Peter's suicide as a trap?
That's low, immoral, even.
I tried to tell you. I always win.
You might have gotten away
with murder, but you didn't win.
How's that exactly?
No matter what you say, I know the truth.
You cared about Peter
and it was your actions
that drove him to kill himself.
That is something that you will live with
for the rest of your life.
- I'll manage.
- No, you won't.
It'll eat you up from the inside
because you cared
way too much about him.
- You're wrong.
- No, I'm right.
Just like I'm right about
the first time I saw you.
You are an open book to me.
You're transparent, like glass.
If you think for a moment I even
remotely cared about Peter
you're as gullible as he was.
Not just cared. You loved him.
I know it. Can't you see?
- There's nothing you can hide from me.
- You're a fool.
And you're a terrible liar.
You lost, Erica, not just some little game.
- You lost someone you loved.
- I didn't love Peter.
I could care less about him.
He... He meant nothing to me.
Perfect. That's exactly
what I was hoping to hear
rather, that's exactly what I
was hoping Peter would hear.
Peter.
Thank God you're here.
Don't listen to a word they say.
They're telling you lies.
You know how I feel about you, darling.
Peter. Peter! Please!
By the way, there
was a body in that bag.
It wasn't Peter's. No, of course not.
That's kind of obvious.
It was your husband's.
And I told you I would
catch you, and I did.
Erica left ten minutes into the interview.
She told me to wait
behind with the recorder.
"She said if I just played the questions"
"then no one would ever know
she was gone."
She knew John was going down
to the marina after work.
That time of day
there aren't a lot of
people around, you know?
"She waited for him and..."
"And you shot him."
You shot your own husband
in cold blood.
Peter told us everything.
You used him as your accomplice
because he was weak, unstable.
You could manipulate him.
But it backfired.
He couldn't take the pressure
and now he'll testify against you
and you will spend a very
long time in prison.
Don't count on it.
It's over.
A jury still has to believe him.
And he is, as you so
accurately put it, unstable.
Erica, it's over.
I'm sure of it.
Don't be.
Not everyone's as smart as you.
"Jane?"
You in here?
Ah, there's my laptop.
"Uh, I'm looking for someone
who, uh..."
"Someone... I can trust"
"someone strong, someone..."
"At peace with themselves"
"someone better than me"
"someone who knows the..."
"Worst side of me and still loves me."
"Sounds like an amazing woman."
"She was."